

Trisha Sumiran COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

- 55-220 Kulanui St, Laie, HI 96762
- trisha.byu@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/ in/trishasumiran/

https://trishaminela.github .io/TrishaMinelaPortfolio/

PROFILE

I'm Trisha Minela, a senior Computer Science student with a fervent passion for web design and object oriented programming. Over the years, I've combined my design prowess with programming acumen to develop websites and programs that bridge aesthetics with functionality.

I also have a background in programming, with expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, C++, Ruby, and Python. This knowledge has allowed me to combine my design skills with programming skills to develop websites and programs that bridge aesthetics with functionality.

Check out my Portfolio: https://trishaminela.github.io/TrishaMi nelaPortfolio/

EDUCATION HISTORY

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Jan 2022 - Dec 2024

Brigham Young University - Hawaii

- Anticipated Graduation (Fall 2024) - GPA 3.9

Advanced Diploma in Travel and Tourism

Feb 2018 - Jan 2020

International Career Institute

- Succeeded course work with a consistent grade of A, focusing on Tourism System and Industry, Products and Operations, and Hospitality and Tourism Management.

HONORS AND AWARDS

Member, Phi Kappa Phi Honor Society Member, Upsilon Pi Epsilon Honor Society

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI DEVELOPER

Zandi Experience Design, LLC Jul - Sep 2024

- Assisting in the development of custom web application solutions for online e-commerce stores.
- Creating custom proof-of-concept projects for various web and mobile applications.

COMPUTER SCIENCE RESEARCH ASSISTANT/ TEACHING ASSISTANT/TUTOR

Brigham Young University Nov 2023 - Present Hawaii

- Assisted students with programming in HTML, CSS, Java, and Python, helping them develop websites and applications.
- Simplified complex computer science concepts to improve students' understanding across multiple languages and frameworks.
- Contributed to the "Temples Timeline" open-source Android application using Java, focusing on maintaining data accuracy and improving functionality.
- Spearheaded the development of a new app version, introducing features and enhancements to improve user experience.

TOUR GUIDE

Polynesian Cultural Center Jan 2022 - Jan 2024

- Ensure that the schedule and tour atmosphere expectations are met.
- Create a personal connection between the guests and the islands of Polynesia.

CUSTOMER SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE

Big Outsource Leasing Co Oct 2019 - Oct 2021

• Performed successfully in handling simultaneous cases under chat support, emails, and phone calls.